http://www.dunbrooke.com/p/privacy-policy

|
(0)
privacy policy
Dunbrooke Apparel Corporation promises to protect the personal information given to us by visitors to our website and information included on our electronic mail lists.
COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION:
Dunbrooke does not sell, loan or trade personal information collected on our website or included on our email lists to any 3rd party. You may unsubscribe from Dunbrooke’s promotional and marketing email lists at any time. You may unsubscribe by calling customer service at (800) 641-3627 or email us at greatservice@dunbrooke.com.
TERMS AND MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY
By using this website you agree to the terms of our privacy policy. Dunbrooke may modify this policy at any time at its discretion and modifications are effective upon being posted on this site. You are responsible for reviewing this privacy policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on the Dunbrooke website, please contact greatservice@dunbrooke.com or call us at (800) 641-3627.
Dunbrooke Apparel Corporation promises to protect the personal information given to us by visitors to our website and information included on our electronic mail lists.
collection of information:
Dunbrooke does not sell, loan or trade personal information collected on our website or included on our email lists to any 3rd party. You may unsubscribe from Dunbrooke’s promotional and marketing email lists at any time. You may unsubscribe by calling customer service at (800) 641-3627 or email us at greatservice@dunbrooke.com.
terms and modifications to policy
By using this website you agree to the terms of our privacy policy. Dunbrooke may modify this policy at any time at its discretion and modifications are effective upon being posted on this site. You are responsible for reviewing this privacy policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on the Dunbrooke website, please contact greatservice@dunbrooke.com or call us at (800) 641-3627.
Quick Links
Home
Our Story
Our Brands
Contact
Order a Catalog
Catalogs & Pricing
FAQ
